Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, 1941-1990 MS2070
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Congressional committee files, 1819-1989; MS2070 Series 4; 12 Linear feet
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Report, House Resolution and Markups on Res. 75, 1981 March 04 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Report, House Resolution 3861, 1984 May 15 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Report, House Resolution 325 (Paper Bound), 1986 May 13 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Report, Briefing Book, 325, 1986 May 13 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Statements, House Resolution 3861, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Subject Reference File, Briefing Materials 4776, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood: legislative history: book, "Legislative History, District of Columbia, Statehood Constitutional Convention", 1985 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Act, House Resolution 497 for the Admission of the States of Iowa and Florida, 1845 February 14 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Act, House Resolution 435, People of Colorado to Form a State, 1874 June 09 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Act, Admission of the State of Vermont, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, Admission of the State of Kentucky, 1790 January 05 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, Admission of the State of Ohio, 1802 April 02 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, Admission of the State of Louisiana, 1812 March 16 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 17, Admission of the State of Maine, 1819 December 21 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 178, Admission of the State of Arkansas, 1836 March 22 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 81, Admission of the State of Michigan, 1836 December 29 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 169, Admission of the State of California, 1850 March 25 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 12707, Admission of the States of Oklahoma, New Mexico and Arizona, 1906 January 20 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 86, Admission of the State of Minnesota, 1858 January 26 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 239, Admission of the State of Oregon, 1858 April 05 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 23, Admission of the State of Kansas, 1860 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S96, Admission of the State of Nevada, 1864 February 08 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 456, Admission of the State of Nebraska, 1866 December 05 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 185, Admission of the State of South Dakota, 1887 December 13 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 892, Admission of the State of Wyoming, 1889 December 18 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 4562, Admission of the State of Idaho, 1890 January 13 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, Admission of the State of Utah, 0618 September93 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, S 50, Admission of the State of Hawaii, 1959 January 09 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, Admission of the State of Tennessee, undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Report, House Resolution 7999, Admission of the State of Alaska, 1957 June 25 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Report, Reference Project Report, Analysis of the Proposed Constitution of the State of New Columbia, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Resolution, Admission of the State of Missouri, 1821 February 16 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Resolution, Admission of the States of New Mexico and Arizona, 1911 August 17 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Subject Reference Files, Statehood for Puerto Rico, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Directory, Statehood Mission Team, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Invitation, Hearing oC. Statehood, 1984 May 15 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Maps, National Capital Planning Commission, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Press Kit, D.C. Statehood, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Program, Statehood Celebration, 1983 May 21 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Resolution, Support Statehood, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Script, Telephone Bank, 1987 December (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Alabama, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Arkansas, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Colorado, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Connecticut, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Florida, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Georgia, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Illinois, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Indiana, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Louisiana, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Mississippi, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-New Jersey, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-North Carolina, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-South Carolina, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Tennessee, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule-Virginia, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Lobby Kit, Home Rule Self Determination for D.C., 1973 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Act, Amended Home Rule Act, 1985 April (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Article, "Potential Black Voter Influence in Congressional Districts", 1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Booklet, "10th Anniversary of D.C. Home Rule, A Decade of Home Rule: The Challenge Continues", 1985 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Campaign Files, Home Rule, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Clippings, D.C. Home Rule Boycott, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Clippings, Home Rule, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: News Release, National Coalition for D.C. Home Rule, 1971 July 29 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Packet, Home Rule Lobby, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Home Rule Lobby file: Remarks, D.C. Citizens Home Rule, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Clippings, House Resolution 4776, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Correspondence, Republican Party Review, 1987 April 21 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Correspondence, Homelessness, 1988 January 12 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Correspondence, House Resolution 4776, 1988 October (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Bill, House Resolution 2402, 1987 May 13 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Bill, House Resolution 4168, 1988 March 16 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Bill, House Resolution 4236, 1988 March 23 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Hearing Files, Bound House Resolution 325, Serial No. 99-19, 1986 May 13-September 30 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Hearing Files, Bound House Resolution 325, Serial No. 99-19, 1986 May 13-September 30 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Hearing Files, St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1987 June 23 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Hearing Files, Ambulance Service & 911, 1987 August 05 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Meeting Files, Statehood House Resolution 51, 1986 May 19 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Meeting Files, Statehood House Resolution 325, 1986 June 11-September 22 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Meeting Files, Statehood 325, 1986 September 30 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Meeting Files, Markups Hearings for House Resolution 51, 1987 May 19 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Report, Hearings and Markups on House Resolution 3671, 1985 November 07-13 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Report, Committee Print of House Resolution 51, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statement, St. Elizabeth's Hospital Meeting, 1983 August 02 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statement, Don Edwards, 1984 May 15 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statement, Walter E. Fauntroy, 1986 May 13-June 11 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statements, Public Law 94-142 and Youth Services, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statement, James Wyke, 1987 March 26 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statements, Subcommittee on Statehood, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Statement, Mark-up of H.R. 1502, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Testimonies, Andrew Brimmer and John Hechinger, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health: Testimony, Marion Barry, 1989 April 13 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Bill House Resolution 2205, 1988 March 23 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Bill, House Resolution 4230, 1988 March 23 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Bill, House Resolution 4307, 1988 March 30 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Bill, House Resolution 4700, 1988 May 26 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Bill, House Resolution 152, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Bill, House Resolution 1502, 1989 March 20 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Statement, WMATA Metrorail System, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Statement, Mark up of H.R. 1463, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Clippings, House Resolution 151 (Traffic Act), 1987 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Correspondence on House Resolution 2909, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs: Summary, Bound Committee Print, "Governance of the Nation's Capital: A Summary History of the Forms and Powers of Local Government for the Distnct of Columbia 1790 to 1973", 1990 November (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Meeting Files, Briefing Materials for House Resolutions 2319, 2637, and 1602, 1983 April 25 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Meeting Files, House Resolution 1502, 1989 June 13 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Organizational Description, Self- Determination for D.C., undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Article, "Congressional Record on Voting Rights", 1978 March 01-02 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Audio Tape, Jingle for D.C. Voting Representation, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Booklet, "A Simple Case of Democracy Denied", Circa 1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Campaign File, Voting Rights, Circa 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Campaign File, Voting Representation, Circa 1978 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Campaign File, Voter Registration Participation Project, 1986 September 27 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Clippings, Voting Rights and House Resolution 554, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Correspondence, Support of House Resolution 554, 1976-1978 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Correspondence, Support of House Resolution 139, 1977 June (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Hearing Files, Bound Hearing on Voting Rights act Part 1, 1981 May-1981 July (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Hearing Files, Bound Record of Hearings on Voting Rights Act Part3, 1981 May-1981 July (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Meeting Files, Task Force on Voting Rights, 1977 May 09-June 27 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: News Release, Voting Rights, 1977-1982 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Proposal, History and Plan of Operations, Circa 1980 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Remarks, House Resolution 554, 1978 March 01 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Report, House Resolution 554, 1978 February 16 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Resolution, D.C. Representation Resolution, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Statement, Full Voting Representation, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Statement, Voting Representation, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Statement, House Resolution 554 and Voting Rights, 1977-1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Statement, Senate Joint Resolution 4, 1980 January 24 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Summary, House Resolution 554, Circa 1978 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Voting Rights Act file: Testimony, House Resolution 554, 1979 January 30 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Report, Report 101-501 on Implementation of the Inter-American Convention on International Commercial Arbitration, 1990 May 31 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Resolution. Joint Resolution 504 to Repeal the Twenty-third Article Amendment to the Constitution of the United States, 1990 March 06 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Subcommittee on the Judiciary: Subject Reference, Lorton Prison, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Subcommittee on Public Health, Welfare, Housing and Youth Affairs: Bill, House Resolution 1734, 1987 March 19 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Public Health, Welfare, Housing and Youth Affairs: Meeting Files, House Resolution 4746, 1986 June 04 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, David Cooke, 1989 August 22 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, Danny Wall, 1989 August 22 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Report, Monetary Policy, 1982 March 31 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Report, Historic Preservations Programs and Agencies in the National Capital Region, 1985 November (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, House Banking Committee Markup of House Resolution 1278, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Act, House Resolution 1720, 1987 December 17 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Amendment, House Resolution 4645, undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Meeting Files, Historic Preservation and Coinage, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Subcommittee Briefing Book, Domestic Monetary Policy, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Subcommittee Briefing Book, Domestic Monetary Policy, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Subcommittee Briefing Book, Domestic Monetary Policy, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Meeting Files, Business and Employment, 1982 October 12 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Meeting Files, Alternative Anti-Inflation Policies, 1982 December 08 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Release, Interest Rates on Local Residents, 1982 February 03 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Release, District Bank Presidents, 1982 September (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Announcement, Congressional Hearing on Employment & Economic Recovery, 1984 March 06 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, Federal Reserve Directors Conference, 1982 March (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Remarks, New Directors of the Federal Reserve District Bank, 1982 April 12 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Release, Multilateral Development Bank, 1989 October 18 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, Markup of International Development and Finance Act, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, Support for Housing Program, 1988 June-1988 July (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, Housing Task Force, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Flyer, D.C. Housing Tour and Legislative Update, 1989 October (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Flyer, D.C. "Housing Now!" Coalition, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Hearing Files, House Resolution 4026 and 4746, 1986 June 04-1988 March 25 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Hearing Files, Amendment to House Resolution 4746, 1986 May 19 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Hearing Files, Summary of Housing and Community Development Act of 1987 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Release, Housing Agency Act, 1983 February 07 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Release, "Housing Now!" Coalition, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Report, "Milestones in Federal Policy: An Update, and New Housing Policy", 1969-1989 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, Housing and Community Development, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, Action to Rehabilitate Community Housing (ARCH), 1987 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, Housing Program for the 101st Congress, 1989 March 06 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, Housing Program, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, "Grass Roots Support for Public Housing Innovation", undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Campaign Files, "Housing Now", 1989 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Clippings, Housing, 1960-1963 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Meeting, Housing Mission Team Workshop, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Newsletter, WCSA Housing Counseling Monitor, 1983 June-1983 July (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, Haitian Affairs, 1983-1988 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Correspondence, Haitian Affairs, National Day of Prayer, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Briefing Book, Re: Haitian Affairs for Fauntroy's Trip to Haiti, 1985 April 08-12 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Briefing Book, re: Haitian Affairs for Fauntroy's Trip to Haiti, 1985 April 08-12 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Releases, Death of Haitian Refugees, 1979 August 23 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Releases, Haitian Refugee Issue, 1980 April 16 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Releases, Refugee Policy, 1980 September 23 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Releases, Arrests and Expulsions from Haiti, 1980 December 09 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: News Releases, Circuit Court of Appeals Ruling on Haitian Refugees and GAO Report Accuses Government of Discrimination Against Haitian Refugees, 1983 April 13-June 17 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Remarks, African and Haitian Refugees, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Remarks, "Haiti, A Real Test for U.S. Policy", undated (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Statement, Fact Finding Mission to Haiti, 1982 December 15-20 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Clippings, "Haiti Closes School..", 1986 January 09 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Meeting Files, Recommended Mission Statement for the 98th Congress on Haitian Affairs: Report on Mission to Haiti; Legislation on Central America and the Caribbean, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs: Resolution, House Joint Resolution 416, Support of Democracy and Respect for Human Rights in Haiti, 1987 December 08 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Congressional Black Caucus (CBC): Address, "A Constructive Alternative Budget", 1981 March 18 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Black Caucus (CBC): Address, Congressional Black Caucus' 11th Annual Legislative Weekend Awards and Dinner Program, 1981 September 26 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Black Caucus (CBC): Address, National Summit Conference on Black Economic Development, 1982 July 26 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Black Caucus (CBC): Brochure, "Legislative Leadership for Black America and A Changing World", Circa 1981 (Box 54, Folder 4)